http://www.leamingtonfc.co.uk/index.php/club/policies/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how Leamington Football Club Limited, Leamington FC Vice-Presidents’ Club & Leamington FC in the Community (collectively “LFC” “us” “our”) use and protect any information that you give LFC.
For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 and from 25 May 2018 the General Data Protection Regulations 2017 (the Act), the data controller is Leamington Football Club Limited a company registered in England with company number 01756713 and whose registered office is Phillips 66 Community Stadium, Harbury Lane, Bishops Tachbrook, Leamington Spa, CV33 9QB. ICO Registration: A8264069.
This policy explains how we collect, store and use your personal data when you visit this website and when you transact with us by telephone, e-mail or otherwise. It also describes the types of data we collect, how we use this data to ensure we provide relevant and timely services to you, and your rights to control our use of that data.
By visiting this website and in providing any data about yourself to us, you are confirming that you have read understood and agree to our policies and consent to us using that information as described. If you are at all uncertain about any aspect of our policies and practices, please contact us at info@leamingtonfc.co.uk or by post at our registered office and refrain from using this website.
We may update this policy from time to time so please check back here regularly. The last update was 18 April 2018.
WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT
Personal data means any information about an individual from which that individual can be identified.
You provide information about yourself when you register with us on the website, and by filling in forms at an event or online, or by corresponding with us by phone, e-mail or otherwise.
The information you give us may vary depending on the service requested.
It may include your name, date of birth, address, e-mail address, phone number, gender, product selections, credit/debit card or other payment information, a password and the contact details of a third party in the case of emergency. We may also ask for relevant health information, which is classed as special category personal data, for the purposes of your health, wellbeing, welfare and safeguarding. Where we hold this data it will be with the explicit consent of the participant or, if applicable, the participant’s parent or guardian.
Where we need to collect personal data to fulfil our responsibilities and you do not provide that data, we may not be able honour or administer your membership.
In order to improve the quality of our services and your experience when visiting our website we also monitor your visit and collect information about where you are on the internet (eg the URL you came from, IP address, domain types like .co.uk and .com), your browser type, the country and telephone area code where your computer is located, the pages of our website that were viewed during your visit, the advertisements you clicked on, and any search terms that you entered on our website ("User Information"). We may collect this information even if you do not register with us.
We are aware that many children will visit leamingtonfc.co.uk and we would always encourage children under the age of 13 to talk with parents or legal guardians before submitting any personal information to this site or on any associated forms. We will always endeavour to seek parental consent for any children under the age of 13 entering personal data for competitions, events and promotions.
WHY WE NEED YOUR PERSONAL DATA
We will only use personal data for any purpose for which it has been specifically provided.
The reason we need participants’ and members’ personal data is to be able to run the football club, arrange matches; to administer memberships, and provide the membership services you are signing up to when you register with us. Our lawful basis for processing your personal data is that we have a contractual obligation to you as a participant or member to provide the services you are registering for.
We have set out below, in a table format, a description of all the ways we plan to use your personal data, and which of the legal bases we rely on to do so. We have also identified what our legitimate interests are where appropriate.
Purpose/ Processing Activity
Lawful Basis for processing under Article 6 of the GDPR.
processing membership forms and payments e.g Season Tickets, Brakes Lottery
Performance of a contract
organising events e.g. fundraising events, holiday camps/events organised by Leamington FC in the Community, football tournaments
Performance of a contract
processing on-line shop orders on our website
Performance of a contract
sharing data with coaches, managers or officials to run training sessions or enter events
Performance of a contract
sharing data with leagues we are in membership of, county associations and other competition providers for entry in events
Performance of a contract
sharing data with committee members to provide information about club activities, membership renewals or invitation to social events
The Club has a legitimate interest to maintain member and participant correspondence for club community purposes.
sharing data with third party service or facility providers
The Club has a legitimate interest to run the organisation efficiently and as it sees fit. Provision of some third party services is for the benefit of the Club, participants and its members.
sharing anonymised data with a funding partner as condition of grant funding e.g. Local Authority
The Club has a legitimate interest to run the organisation efficiently and as it sees fit. Application for funding is a purpose that benefits the Club, participants and its members.
publishing match and league results
Consent. We will only publish your personal data in a public domain, including images and names, if you have given your consent for us to do so. In the case of children under the age of 13 then only with written consent of parent/guardian
sending out marketing information such as newsletters and information about promotions and offers
Consent. We will only send you direct marketing if you are an existing member, participant or other associated individual and you have not previously objected to this marketing, or, you have actively provided your consent.
To ensure we understand possible health risks e.g. Participants in community scheme events
Consent. We will only process details on your medical history with your consent.
WHO WE SHARE YOUR PERSONAL DATA WITH
As part of offering these services we may at times be required to transfer some of your data to third parties for processing to enable fulfilment of product purchases or provision of services. This will be limited to that which they need to carry out their services and only in the way in which we instruct them as part of a contractual agreement. Your data will never be sold or shared with third parties for the purposes of marketing without seeking prior consent. This would be separate to the consent provided as part of registration to this site.
We may disclose your personal information to third parties to comply with a legal obligation; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of our participants, members or affiliates, or others.
The Club’s data processing may require your personal data to be transferred outside of the UK. Where the Club does transfer your personal data overseas it is with the sufficient appropriate safeguards in place to ensure the security of that personal data.
PROTECTION OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA
We have put in place appropriate security measures to prevent your personal data from being accidentally lost, used or accessed in an unauthorised way, altered or disclosed.
HOW LONG WE HOLD YOUR PERSONAL DATA
We keep personal data on our participants and members while they continue to be a participant or member or are otherwise actively involved with the Club. We will delete this data after a participant or member has left or otherwise ended their membership or affiliation, or sooner if specifically requested and we are able to do so. We may need to retain some personal data for longer for legal or regulatory purposes.
YOUR RIGHTS CONCERNING YOUR PERSONAL DATA
As a data subject you may have the right at any time to request access to, rectification or erasure of your personal data; to restrict or object to certain kinds of processing of your personal data, including direct marketing; to the portability of your personal data and to complain to the UK’s data protection supervisory authority, the Information Commissioner’s Office about the processing of your personal data.
As a data subject you are not obliged to share your personal data with us. If you choose not to share your personal data with us we may not be able to register or administer your membership.
If you have any questions about this Privacy Notice then please contact info@leamingtonfc.co.uk or write to our Registered address: The Phillips 66 Community Stadium, Harbury Lane, Leamington Spa, CV33 9QB.
©
2020
Leamington Football Club Ltd
Privacy Policy
